Cat in the box
3-5 Players (best 4)
20 - 40 Min 
Age: 8+ 
needs -  
          2x deck of cards
          3-5x player boards.   See below
	  1x research board.    See below
          11-14 Tokens of different colours for each player

https://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/345972/cat-box-deluxe-edition

https://github.com/MndBlade/games/blob/main/card%20games/cat%20in%20the%20box/cat%20in%20the%20box%20player%20card.pdf
https://github.com/MndBlade/games/blob/main/card%20games/cat%20in%20the%20box/cat%20in%20the%20box%20research%20card.pdf

Setup 
    Players           cards                                 research board.   Player boards
        3                 5x(A-6)  = 30 cards           either                        2/3
        4                 5x(A-8)  = 40 cards           either                        4/5
        5                 5x(A-9)  = 45 cards           diagonal                    4/5
        


Deal all the cards. Everyone discards 1 card before bidding. 
Bid how many tricks you expect to take, starting with start player. 
Play the tricks, skip the last card. Can't lead trump until it's broken. Stop immediately if there's a Paradox, and this trick is not awarded. 
Playing tricks
Rule 1: In the row of the color you are declaring ontheresearch board,the played card number's space must be empty.
Rule 2: On your player board, X of the color you are declaring is not revealed.
Start player
You may only declare blue, yelow, or green *Exception: If any token is placed on the red row of research board, you may declare red
Following players
You may declare any color.
If you declare any colour other than the led remove your player token of the led color on your player board, revealing X

Paradox
A paradox occurs when declaring the observed color cannot be met.
•Reveal your hand and declare a paradox - Immediately proceed to the scoring phase
Scoring when causing a paradox
Scores from tricks: -1 point for each trick Bonus score: forfeited


Score: 1 point per trick. (Score negative if you caused the Paradox.)
add your bonus if you matched your bid. (No bonus if you caused the Paradox.)
1 point for each token in the largest group of your player tokens connected adjacently on the research board
